name: 'Past Simple: have, get, go'
questions:
  -
    question: 'She $ cereal for breakfast yesterday.'
    answers:
      - has
      - haved
      - had
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ to the movies last week?'
    answers:
      - 'Did you went'
      - 'Did you go'
      - 'Do you went'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'We $ lunch.'
    answers:
      - 'didn''t had'
      - 'didn''t have'
      - 'don''t had'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'What time $?'
    answers:
      - 'did the children get up?'
      - 'the children got up?'
      - 'did the children got up?'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'I $ to bed at 9:30!'
    answers:
      - 'did go'
      - 'did went'
      - went
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'Jane $ to her English class yesterday.'
    answers:
      - 'didn''t want'
      - 'don''t went'
      - 'didn''t go'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'What $ for lunch today?'
    answers:
      - 'did you have'
      - 'did you had'
      - 'you had'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'He $ to school by bus last week.'
    answers:
      - 'didn''t went'
      - 'didn''t go'
      - 'don''t went'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'They $ home at 8:00.'
    answers:
      - 'did go'
      - 'did went'
      - went
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ to the gym last week?'
    answers:
      - 'Did they went'
      - 'Did they go'
      - 'Do they went'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'I $ at 12:00 today!'
    answers:
      - 'got up'
      - 'did get up'
      - 'did got up'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: '$ your homework?'
    answers:
      - 'Did you do'
      - 'Did you'
      - 'Do you did'
    correct: 1
